<quiz>
    <question>
        <text>A software application firm is strengthening its cyber defense by incorporating deception technologies into its framework. How can the utilization of a honeynet benefit the software application firm's strategy?</text>
        <options>
            <option>It is a decoy system that mimics natural systems or applications at a more finite level to monitor attacker activity.</option>
            <option>It creates fake files appearing to contain sensitive information, capturing data on attempts to access and steal data.</option>
            <option>It creates false credentials, login credentials, or other data types to distract and gain insight into attackers.</option>
			<option correct="true">It uses a network of decoy systems to simulate an entire network to capture attackers' tactics and tools.</option>
        </options>
    </question>
    <question>
        <text>An organization has an established change management program that includes standard operating procedures (SOPs). It wants to implement changes consistently and effectively. What role do SOPs play in the change management process?</text>
        <options>
            <option>They help track and communicate the status and outcome of approved changes.</option>
            <option correct="true">They define routine operations or changes, providing detailed instructions to implement them.</option>
            <option>They outline the steps for employees to follow when conducting an impact analysis.</option>
			<option>They provide guidelines for developing backout plan procedures for changes.</option>
        </options>
    </question>
	<question>
        <text>A user in a company wants a new USB flash drive. Rather than requesting one through the proper channel, the user obtains one from one of the company's storage closets. Upon approaching the closet door, the user notices a warning sign indicating cameras are in use. What is the control objective of the observed sign?</text>
        <options>
            <option>Detective</option>
            <option>Preventive</option>
            <option correct="true">Deterrent</option>
			<option>Corrective</option>
        </options>
    </question>
	<question>
        <text>A systems owner reviews permissions granted to a targeted team of employees and determines that some of the employees' accesses are outside their scope of work. After revoking the certificates, what log does the owner use to record the changes?</text>
        <options>
            <option>Public Key Infrastructure (PKI)</option>
            <option correct="true">Certificate Revocation Lists (CRL)</option>
            <option>Trusted Platform Module (TPM)</option>
			<option>Hardware Security Module (HSM)</option>
        </options>
    </question>
	<question>
        <text>The organization is implementing a significant software upgrade that necessitates application restarts. How can the cybersecurity analyst ensure a smooth transition without causing extended downtime?</text>
        <options>
            <option>Conduct the software upgrade without restarting the applications to avoid interruptions.</option>
            <option correct="true">Schedule the upgrade during nonworking hours to reduce the impact on users.</option>
            <option>Restart all applications simultaneously to complete the upgrade faster.</option>
			<option>Implement the upgrade without analyzing software dependencies.</option>
        </options>
    </question>
	
	<question>
        <text multi="true">In a cybersecurity operation where minimizing downtime is critical to its mission, a cybersecurity analyst incorporates allowlists and denylists restrictions. The objective is to guarantee high availability (HA) and safeguard against potential security threats. How would a cybersecurity analyst utilize these lists in this scenario? (Select the two best options.)</text>
        <options>
            <option correct="true">Allowlists can specify approved software, hardware, and change types that are essential for the operation's functioning.</option>
            <option>Denylists can restrict changes that require rigorous testing and approval to prevent any potential disruptions to the operation.</option>
            <option>Allowlists can include authorized software and hardware updates that are preapproved for installation to ensure operational continuity.</option>
			<option correct="true">Denylists can block unauthorized software, hardware, and change types that pose high risk to the operation's availability and security.</option>
        </options>
    </question>

</quiz>